nhpr.org 2003-06-15

# Privacy Policy

|  |    

89.1, Concord, WEVO   
90.3, Nashua, WEVO   
90.7, Keene, WEVN   
91.3, Littleton, WEVO   
91.3, Hanover, WEVH   
99.5, Jackson, WEVJ   
104.3, Dover, WEVO   
107.1, Berlin, WEVC  
  
---|---  
History of NHPR | Newsletter | Board of Trustees | Community Advisory Board | Staff | Jobs | Internships | Financial Information | Volunteer | Privacy Policy | Contact NHPR

## Privacy Information:

This statement discloses the privacy practices for New Hampshire Public Radio. Your personal privacy is important -- very important. But depending on how you use our web site, you may decide to give us certain personal information. We want you to know that we treat that information with as much concern for your privacy as we do when you call us to make a pledge and become a member. Please read the details in the sections below. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact the [New Media Coordinator](mailto:webmaster@nhpr.org)   

### On-Line Pledging 

When you support NHPR on-line, we use the SSL system which encrypts all information you enter on the donation form. That information is then decoded at the receiving end. We contract with a third-party company to operate this system but any information you send to us ends up only at NHPR. 

All information you send to NHPR is used solely for NHPR communication purposes. We share your name with no other organizations. Period. 

If you choose to receive no further communications from NHPR, you have the option to do so. If you don't choose that option, from time to time we may ask for your opinions on ideas we have regarding our services or notify you of some new feature we offer on our web site. You can choose to stop receiving these notices at any time by contacting the [Director of New Media.](mailto:webmaster@nhpr.org)

### Web Registration

If you choose to participate in any NHPR on-line discussions you will be asked to fill out a registration form and indicate that you agree to observe the basic rules of common politeness that make for a good exchange of ideas. 

You might choose to receive e-mail notification when new comments are posted to a particular discussion. As technology permits, you might have the option to be notified when we produce programs on a particular subject. The information you give us is used strictly for NHPR communications. 

You are in full control of any e-mail notices you receive. You can stop them at any time by coming to the NHPR web site and changing your personal preference information. If in the course of an on-line discussion you post your e-mail address or any other personal information on the NHPR web site, you should be aware that others will then be able to send you e-mail at that address. 

NHPR strongly advises that you never put your e-mail address on the web; we cannot be held responsible if you choose to do so. 

Any material posted on the NHPR web site grants a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable right to sue, reproduce, modify, publish, create derivative works from, distribute and display such postings in any media. Also, you grant us the right to use whatever name you submit with whatever you post. Your ownership or control over all of the rights to the materials you post is warranted and represented by you. You warrant that the use by NHPR will not infringe upon or violate the rights of any third party. 

### Record Removal

If you want to have all information related to you removed from our web-related registration system, send an email to the [Director of New Media ](mailto:webmaster@nhpr.org)and your information will be deleted. 

### Cookies

We use cookies to recognize you and to track how you use NHPR's web site. But please note: Cookies simply distinguish between anonymous user A and anonymous user B. They do not allow us to identify you personally or follow your personal usage of the NHPR web site. 

Cookies are bits of information that sit on your computer. You can adjust your browser (Netscape, Internet Explorer, Opera, etc) to refuse cookies. The information we collect lets us know how many people use our site and which parts of the site they use most often. 

### IP Addresses

The NHPR web site also logs IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behavior on our site. 

### Compliance with Legal Process

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the NHPR web site; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions). 

### Links to other web sites 

NHPR is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of Web sites to which it may link. 

### Changes to these privacy policies

These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. 

Any such changes will be posted on this page. If the changes represent a material departure from our current practices with respect to the use of personal information, the changes will be posted on this page thirty days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via email. 

207 North Main Street, Concord, NH 03301-5003   
phone 603.228.8910   fax 603.224.6052   

|
